Evheniy Hrechukhin

Front-End Developer

Contacts:

tel: +38(096)404-58-40

email: hrechukhin@gmail.com

<u>Linkedin</u> <u>GitHub</u>

Summary:

Around 2+ of experience in developing User Interfaces for Mobile/Tablet/Desktop using **HTML**, **CSS**, **TypeScript**, **JavaScript**, **jQuery**, **Bootstrap**.

Experience in developing applications in a single page (SPAs) using framework **Angular**.

Good Understanding of **Document Object Model (DOM)** and **DOM Functions**.

Experience of working on CSS Preprocessors like SCSS.

Experience in Front-End tooling workflows Node JS (NPM or YARN), Gulp and Webpack.

Experience in GitHub, and Bitbucket for source code management and for version control.

Expertise in using IDE's like WebStorm and Visual Studio.

Experience in working with different operating systems like Windows and Linux.

Excellent interpersonal abilities, communication skills, time management and Team skills with an intention to work hard to meet project deadlines.

Technical Skills:

Web Technologies: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, AJAX, jQuery, SCSS.

Frameworks: Angular.

Programming Languages: JavaScript, TypeScript.

Version Control System: GIT.

Operating Systems: Windows, Linux.

IDE: Visual Studio Code, WebStorm.

Others: Ngx-Bootstrap, RxJs, Webpack, Gulp.

Professional Experience:

BeKey (August 2019 – Present)

Responsibilities:

Responsible for creating efficient design and developing User Interaction screens using HTML, CSS3, Bootstrap, TypeScript, Angular.

Experience with **Angular** to develop single page applications.

Created **Typescript** reusable components and services to consume **REST API's** using Component-based architecture provided by **Angular**.

Experience with creating custom directives, decorators, and services to interface with restful.

Implemented HTTP requests using RxJs Observable library to handle multiple values over time.

Implemented **Angular Router** to enable navigation from one view to the next as the customer performs application tasks.

Worked on GIT as a version control.

Developed using **Agile Scrum** methodology by breaking down the project to several sprints.

Environment: HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, SASS, Angular, ES6, TypeScript, JSON, XML, Git.

Jose Art Gallery (November 2017 – August 2019)

Responsibilities:

Develop dynamic and multi-browser compatible pages using HTML, CSS, JQuery, JavaScript.

Extensive usage of **Bootstrap** for layout as well as responsive design and **SASS** for Responsive design.

Used **AJAX**, **JSON** to send requests to the server to check the functionality of the websites and for storing and exchanging information between browsers and servers.

Using CSS preprocessor SASS to make CSS more efficient.

Worked on Cross-Browser compatibility and fixed the bugs for several browsers.

Developed the user interface for back office support and worked collaboratively in an agile scrum team on the design and development of application.

Environment: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Bootstrap, jQuery, SASS, AJAX, JSON, RESTful, JIRA, Agile scrum.

Education

Kharkiv National University of Construction and Architecture

(September 2007 – June 2013)

Heat supply and exploitation of secondary heat energy resources

Hobbies & Interests

Front-End;

Table Tennis.